{
"question": "外国",
"answer": "がいこく"
},
{
"question": "小さい",
"answer": "ちいさい"
},
{
"question": "元気",
"answer": "げんき"
},
{
"question": "弟",
"answer": "おとうと"
},
{
"question": "魚",
"answer": "さかな"
},
{
"question": "今年",
"answer": "ことし"
},
{
"question": "お母さん",
"answer": "おかあさん"
},
{
"question": "男の子",
"answer": "おとこのこ"
},
{
"question": "飛ぶ",
"answer": "とぶ"
},
{
"question": "売る",
"answer": "うる"
},
{
"question": "静か",
"answer": "しずか"
},
{
"question": "休む",
"answer": "やすむ"
},
{
"question": "食べ物",
"answer": "たべもの"
},
{
"question": "大切",
"answer": "たいせつ"
},
{
"question": "来週",
"answer": "らいしゅう"
},
{
"question": "警官",
"answer": "けいかん"
},
{
"question": "建物",
"answer": "たてもの"
},
{
"question": "暖かい",
"answer": "あたたかい"
},
{
"question": "降りる",
"answer": "おりる"
},
{
"question": "止まる",
"answer": "とまる"
},
